ILGWU International Relations Department publications 5780/062 PUBS
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Box: 24, Folder: 2, Publication (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Item 14: The Prison Situation, Publication (Box 24, Folder 2)
- Box: 24, Folder: 3, Publication (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Annual Report (1992), Publication (Box 24, Folder 3)
    By National Endowment for Democracy. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Challenges to Democracy in the New Era, Publication (Box 24, Folder 3)
    By National Endowment for Democracy. Summer, 1993. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Challenges to Democracy in the New Era, Publication (Box 24, Folder 3)
    By National Endowment for Democracy. 4th World Conference on Democracy April 26-27, 1993. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Endowment Convenes Meeting for Democracy Foundations, Publication (Box 24, Folder 3)
    By National Endowment for Democracy. Spring, 1993. Item is in English.
- Box: 24, Folder: 4, Publication (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: LIGA News, Publication (Box 24, Folder 4)
    By Democratic League of Free Trade Unions. no.7. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: LIGA News, Publication (Box 24, Folder 4)
    By Democratic League of Free Trade Unions. Extra (no date provided). Item is in English.
  - Item 3: LIGA News; Hungarian Labour Delegation at ILO Conference, Publication (Box 24, Folder 4)
    By Democratic League of Free Trade Unions. no.6. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: LIGA News; May Day, Publication (Box 24, Folder 4)
    By Democratic League of Free Trade Unions. no.5. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: LIGA News; May Day of Free Unions in People's Park, Publication (Box 24, Folder 4)
    By Democratic League of Free Trade Unions. no.4. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: LIGA News; The LIGA is Growing, Publication (Box 24, Folder 4)
    By Democratic League of Free Trade Unions. no.3. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: LIGA News; We Need Solidarity, Publication (Box 24, Folder 4)
    By Democratic League of Free Trade Unions. no.2. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: LIGA News; We Need Solidarity, Publication (Box 24, Folder 4)
    By Democratic League of Free Trade Unions. no.1. Item is in English.
- Box: 24, Folder: 5, Publication (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Garment Worker, Publication (Box 24, Folder 5)
    By National Union of Tailors and Garment Workers (NUTGW). July 1989. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Garment Worker, Publication (Box 24, Folder 5)
    By National Union of Tailors and Garment Workers (NUTGW). February/March 1991. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Garment Worker, Publication (Box 24, Folder 5)
    By National Union of Tailors and Garment Workers (NUTGW). July/August 1990. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Garment Worker, Publication (Box 24, Folder 5)
    By National Union of Tailors and Garment Workers (NUTGW). October 1990. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Garment Worker, Publication (Box 24, Folder 5)
    By National Union of Tailors and Garment Workers (NUTGW). November 1990. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Garment Worker, Publication (Box 24, Folder 5)
    By National Union of Tailors and Garment Workers (NUTGW). December 1990. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Garment Worker, Publication (Box 24, Folder 5)
    By National Union of Tailors and Garment Workers (NUTGW). January 1990. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Garment Worker, Publication (Box 24, Folder 5)
    By National Union of Tailors and Garment Workers (NUTGW). March 1990. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Garment Worker, Publication (Box 24, Folder 5)
    By National Union of Tailors and Garment Workers (NUTGW). May/June 1990. Item is in English.
- Box: 24, Folder: 6, Publication (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Threads, Publication (Box 24, Folder 6)
    By GMB Clothing and Textile Section. no.1 (1991:June). Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Threads, Publication (Box 24, Folder 6)
    By GMB Clothing and Textile Section. no.2 (1991:Sep.). Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Threads, Publication (Box 24, Folder 6)
    By GMB Clothing and Textile Section. no.6 (1992:Oct.). Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Threads, Publication (Box 24, Folder 6)
    By GMB Clothing and Textile Section. no.7 (1992:Dec.). Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Threads, Publication (Box 24, Folder 6)
    By GMB Clothing and Textile Section. no.4 (1992:Mar.). Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Threads, Publication (Box 24, Folder 6)
    By GMB Clothing and Textile Section. no.5 (1992:July). Item is in English.
- Box: 24, Folder: 7, Publication (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: ILGWU, Publication (Box 24, Folder 7)
    By Worker-Family Education Program. English as a Second Language student magazine. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Interviewing our Companeros, Publication (Box 24, Folder 7)
    By ILGWU (International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union). English as a Second Language student magazine. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Students in Action, Publication (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Item 4: The Rising Sun, Publication (Box 24, Folder 7)
- Box: 24, Folder: 8, Publication (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Uncaptive Minds: A journal of information and opintion on Eastern Europe, Publication (Box 24, Folder 8)
    v.4:no.1(15) (1991:Spring). Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Uncaptive Minds: A journal of information and opintion on Eastern Europe, Publication (Box 24, Folder 8)
    v.4:no.2(16) (1991:Summer). Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Uncaptive Minds: A journal of information and opintion on Eastern Europe, Publication (Box 24, Folder 8)
    v.4:no.3(17) (1991:Fall). Item is in English.
- Box: 24, Folder: 9, Publication (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Worldwide Newsletter: December 1989 ed., Publication (Box 24, Folder 9)
    By IRC (International Rescue Committee). v.3 (1989:Dec.). Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Worldwide Newsletter: December 1989 ed., Publication (Box 24, Folder 9)
    By IRC (International Rescue Committee). v.3 (1989:Dec.). Copy 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Worldwide Newsletter: June, 1990 ed., Publication (Box 24, Folder 9)
    By IRC (International Rescue Committee). v.2:no.3 (1988:Nov.). Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Worldwide Newsletter: November 1988 ed., Publication (Box 24, Folder 9)
    By IRC (International Rescue Committee). v.4 (1990:June). Item is in English.
- Box: 24, Folder: 10, Publication (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Across The Table, Publication (Box 24, Folder 10)
    By The Center For Labor-Management Policy Studies. v.2:no.1 (1989:Fall). Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Across The Table, Publication (Box 24, Folder 10)
    By The Center For Labor-Management Policy Studies. v3:no.2 (1991:Fall). Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Across The Table, Publication (Box 24, Folder 10)
    By The Center For Labor-Management Policy Studies. v.4:no.1 (1992:Summer). Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Across The Table, Publication (Box 24, Folder 10)
    By The Center For Labor-Management Policy Studies. v.1:no.4 (1989:Summer). Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Across The Table, Publication (Box 24, Folder 10)
    By The Center For Labor-Management Policy Studies. v.2:no.4 (1991:Spring). Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Across The Table, Publication (Box 24, Folder 10)
    By The Center For Labor-Management Policy Studies. v.3:no.1 (1991:Summer). Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Across The Table, Publication (Box 24, Folder 10)
    By The Center For Labor-Management Policy Studies. Item is in English.
- Box: 24, Folder: 11, Publication (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: NDI Reports, Publication (Box 24, Folder 11)
    Spring 1990. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: NDI Reports, Publication (Box 24, Folder 11)
    Winter 1990. Item is in English.
- Box: 25, Folder: 1, Publication (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Withdrawl Pains: General Moters and Ford Disinvest From South Africa, Publication (Box 25, Folder 1)
    By Glenn Adler. Occasional Papers no.6, November 1989. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Worker Democracy in Socialist France, Publication (Box 25, Folder 1)
    By Bernard E. Brown. Occasional Papers no.7, November 1, 1989. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: A Symposium: Future of Trade Unions in The United States, Publication (Box 25, Folder 1)
    Occasional Papers no.1, Februrary 9, 1988. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: A Symposium: Labor and the Media: How and Why They Grew Estranged, Publication (Box 25, Folder 1)
    Occasional Papers no.2, March 8, 1988. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Home Care and Home Care Workers in Five Countries Britain, Sweden, Norway, Denmark, and Canada, Publication (Box 25, Folder 1)
    By Sumner M. Rosen. Occasional Papers no.5, May 1988. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Labor Market Issues and Policies, Publication (Box 25, Folder 1)
    By Victor Gotbaum; Carol O'Cleireacain. Occasional Papers no.3, May 1, 1989. Item is in English.
- Box: 25, Folder: 2, Publication (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Argentine Rank and File Unionists and Their World, Publication (Box 25, Folder 2)
    By Peter Ranis. Occasional Papers no.9, June 1990. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Competititve Advantage On The Shop Floor: Organization and Technology in Capitalist Development, Publication (Box 25, Folder 2)
    By William Lazonick. Occasional Papers no.10, July 1990. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Worker Democracy in Socialst France, Publication (Box 25, Folder 2)
    By Bernard E. Brown. Occasional Papers no.7, November 1, 1989. Copy 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Worker Insurgency, Radical Organization, and New Deal Labor Legislation, Publication (Box 25, Folder 2)
    By Michael Goldfield. Occasional Papers no.8, April 1990. Item is in English.
- Box: 25, Folder: 3, Publication (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Courier: Provoking Thought and Dialogue About The World, Publication (Box 25, Folder 3)
    no.14 (1993:Fall). Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Global Changes and Domestic Transformations: New Possibilities for American Foreign Policy, Publication (Box 25, Folder 3)
    Vantage Conference 1992. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Global Changes and Domestic Transformations: The Midwest and the World: Vantage Conference 1993, Publication (Box 25, Folder 3)
    Vantage Conference 1993. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: International Human Rights and US Foreign Policy, Publication (Box 25, Folder 3)
    33rd Strategy for Peace, US Foreign Policy Conference 1992. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: State of the United Nations; Decline or Regeneration in the Next Fifty Years, Publication (Box 25, Folder 3)
    29th UN of the Next Decade Conference 1994. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: The Role and Composition of the Security Council, Publication (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Item 7: The Stanley Foundation, Publication (Box 25, Folder 3)
    Flyer. Item is in English.
- Box: 25, Folder: 4, Publication (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Annual Meeting of The Board of Trustees, Publication (Box 25, Folder 4)
    By American Institute For Free Labor Development. May 8, 1986. Item is in English.
- Box: 25, Folder: 5, Publication (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Annual Meeting of the Board of Trustees, Publication (Box 25, Folder 5)
    By American Institute For Free Labor Development. May 8, 1986. Copy 2. Item is in English.
- Box: 25, Folder: 6, Publication (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Building Profiles of Public and Private Companies: Manual of Corporate Investigation, Publication (Box 25, Folder 6)
    By Food and Allied Service Trades. Revised Ed, 1989. Item is in English.
- Box: 25, Folder: 7, Publication (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Safe Work in a Safe World: Interfacing Facts; The Context of ICEF Policy-Making, Publication (Box 25, Folder 7)
    By International Federation of Chemical, Energy and General Workers' Unions. XIX Satatutory Congress Tokyo 7-9 December 1988. Item is in English.
- Box: 25, Folder: 8, Publication (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Betraying the Trust: The Pittson Company's Drive to Break Appalachia's Coalfield Communities, Publication (Box 25, Folder 8)
    By United Mine Workers of America. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Jewish Labor Committee Review, Publication (Box 25, Folder 8)
    By Jewish Labor Committee. Fall 1989. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: United Mine Workers Journal, Publication (Box 25, Folder 8)
    By United Mine Workers of America. 100th Year:no.6 (1989:June). Item is in English.
- Box: 26, Folder: 1, Publication (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Labour: Review of Labour Economics and Industrial Relations, Publication (Box 26, Folder 1)
    By Chris Jecchinis. v.8:no.3 (1994:Autumn). Item is in English.
- Box: 26, Folder: 2, Publication (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: New Views on North-South Relations and Foreign Assistance, Publication (Box 26, Folder 2)
    By Charles F. Doran; Joan M. Nelson; Thomas M. Callaghy; Ingomar Hauchler. Walter Sterling Surrey Memorial Series, NPA no.264. Item is in English.
- Box: 26, Folder: 3, Publication (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Struggle Against Unemployment: the Issues for United Action, Publication (Box 26, Folder 3)
- Box: 26, Folder: 4, Publication (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: The Future of Textiles in Europe, Publication (Box 26, Folder 4)
    By European Parliament Social Group. Item is in English.
- Box: 26, Folder: 5, Publication (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Threadbare: How the Rich Stitch UP the World's Rag Trade, Publication (Box 26, Folder 5)
    By Ben Jackson. Item is in English.
- Box: 26, Folder: 6, Publication (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: IFJ Information: Freelances: A World Wide Survey, Publication (Box 26, Folder 6)
    By International Federation of Journalists. no.36 (1987/1988). Item is in English.
- Box: 26, Folder: 7, Publication (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Changing Role of Trade Unions in Developing Economies, Publication (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Item 2: Trade Union Information Bulletin, Publication (Box 26, Folder 7)
    By Trade Union Division of the Comission of the European Communities. no.2 (1989). Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Trade Union Report on Chemical Weapons, Publication (Box 26, Folder 7)
    By International Federation of Chemical, Energy, and General Workers' Unions. Item is in English.
- Box: 26, Folder: 8, Publication (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: 1993 Democracy Award Dinner, Publication (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Item 2: Activities 1989, Publication (Box 26, Folder 8)
    By National Democratic Institute for International Affairs. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Annual Report: Fiscal and Program Year 1989, Publication (Box 26, Folder 8)
    By Foreign Policy Association. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Briefing Paper: Getting Rid of the Trade Deficit: A Cheaper Dollar Is Not Enough, Publication (Box 26, Folder 8)
    By Jeff Faux. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: North American Agreement on Labor Cooperation Annual Report, Publication (Box 26, Folder 8)
    By U.S. National Administrative Office. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Sweatshops 1995: Unions Fight Back: ILGWU Photographs Teachers Guide, Publication (Box 26, Folder 8)
    By Sue Coe. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: The State of Working America, Publication (Box 26, Folder 8)
    By Lawrence Mishel; Jacqueline Simon. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: The United States and the World: A Conference Committee for the Free World, Publication (Box 26, Folder 8)
    By Committee for the Free World. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Years of Devastation, Publication (Box 26, Folder 8)
    By Economic Researcy Department. Item is in English.
- Box: 26, Folder: 9, Publication (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: The Death of Trees, Publication (Box 26, Folder 9)
    By Vic Thrope. Item is in English.
- Box: 26, Folder: 10, Publication (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Essai sur une Politique De L'Economie Sociale du troisieme secteur vecu au troisieme secteur voulu, Publication (Box 26, Folder 10)
    By Jacques Moreau. Item is in French.
  - Item 2: La Confederation Force Ouvriere, Publication (Box 26, Folder 10)
    By Confederation Force Ouvriere. Item is in French.
- Box: 26, Folder: 11, Publication (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: American Labor ORT Tribute to Evelyn Dubrow: Recipient American ORT Federation Community Achievement Award, Publication (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Item 2: Report to the Community: ORT Training Opens the Doors Of Opportunity for People Throughout the World, Publication (Box 26, Folder 11)
- Box: 26, Folder: 12, Publication (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Economic Integration Development, and Democracy: An International Conference, Publication (Box 26, Folder 12)